muvee.com 2009-02-17

# muvee - Instant Home Movie-Making & Photo Slideshow Software - Copyright Notice and Privacy Statement

## COPYRIGHT NOTICE

Copyright 2005 muvee Technologies Pte. Ltd. All rights reserved. muvee Technologies and its logotype are registered trademarks of muvee Technologies Pte. Ltd. in the US and other countries. All other trademarks are the property of their respective owners.

## PRIVACY STATEMENT

muvee Technologies Pte. Ltd. (“muvee”) and its subsidiaries respect your privacy and are committed to protecting it. muvee has provided this Privacy Statement to inform you of our Privacy Policy and practices and of the choices you can make about the way your information is collected online and how that information is used. We have organized our websites so that, in general, you can visit muvee on the Web without identifying yourself or revealing any personal information. We make this notice readily available on our home page and at the bottom of every muvee web page.

  1. ### Sites covered by this Privacy Statement

This Privacy Statement applies to all muvee.com-owned websites and domains, and our wholly owned subsidiaries (“muvee websites”)

The muvee websites may provide links to third-party websites for your convenience and information. If you access those links, you will leave the muvee website. muvee does not control those sites or their privacy practices, which may differ from muvee’s. We do not endorse or make any representations about third-party websites. The personal data you choose to give to unrelated third parties is not covered by the muvee Privacy Statement. We encourage you to review the privacy policy of any company before submitting your personal information. Some third-party companies may choose to share their personal data with muvee; that sharing is governed by that third-party company’s privacy policy.

  2. ### Types of information we collect

This Privacy Statement covers personal information, non-personal data collection and aggregate reporting.

Personal information is information that is associated with your name or personal identity. muvee uses personal information to understand better your needs and interests and to provide you with better service. Once you choose to provide us with personal information, you can be assured it will be used only to support your customer relationship with muvee. We take seriously the trust you place in us. muvee will not sell, rent or lease your personal information to others.

On some muvee websites or those of our online transaction partner, you can order products or services, request information, subscribe to marketing or support materials, register yourself or your muvee products, or apply for a job opportunity with muvee. The types of personal information you provide to us on these pages may include name, address, phone number, e-mail address, user IDs and passwords, billing and transaction information, credit card information, contact preferences, educational and employment background, and job interest data.

To personalize our websites, services or communications and improve our products and services, we may also ask you to provide us with information regarding your personal or professional interests, demographics, and experiences with our products or services. Providing this additional information is optional.

Non-personal information is data about usage and service operation that is not associated with a specific personal identity. muvee collects and analyzes non-personal information to evaluate how visitors use the muvee websites.

Non-personal data we collect may include the pages visited on the muvee websites, unique URLs visited within www.muvee.com, browser type and IP address. Most non-personal data is collected via cookies or other analysis technologies. muvee Web pages use cookies and other technologies for data analysis and personalization services. muvee also places ads on other websites that may use cookies.

  3. ### Children’s privacy

muvee is committed to protecting the privacy needs of children and we encourage parents and guardians to take an active role in their children’s online activities and interests. muvee does not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13 and muvee does not target its websites to children under 13.

  4. ### How we use your information

muvee uses your personal information to provide you with services and to help us better understand your needs and interests. Specifically, we use your information to help you complete a transaction or order, to communicate with you, to provide service and support, to update you on services and benefits, to personalize promotional offers and to personalize some muvee websites and those of our online transaction partner. Occasionally we may also use your information to contact you for market research regarding muvee products or services. We will give you the opportunity to choose your privacy preferences regarding such communications (see section 7, “Your privacy preferences and opting out”). Credit card information is used only for payment processing and fraud prevention. Credit card information and sensitive personal data are not used for any other purpose by our online transaction partner or muvee and will not be kept longer than necessary for providing the services, unless you ask us to retain your credit card information for future purchases.

Personal data collected online may also be combined with information you provide muvee through other sources such as product registration, call centers or public events such as trade shows or seminars. 

Personal data given to muvee may be transferred across state and country borders for the purposes of data consolidation, storage and simplified customer information management.

Non-personal data is aggregated for reporting about muvee website usability, performance and effectiveness. It is used to improve the customer experience, usability and site content.

  5. ### Who we share your information with

muvee will not sell, rent or lease your personal information to others. muvee will not share your personal information with third parties except in responding to your requests for products or services. Your permission will be requested when you submit your information. muvee shares customer information across muvee-owned business entities and companies working on our behalf, but only as described above in “How we use your information.”

muvee contracts with third-party service providers and suppliers to deliver complete products, services and customer solutions described in “How we use your information.” Suppliers and service providers are required to keep confidential the information received on behalf of muvee and may not use it for any purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing for muvee. These service providers may change or we may contract with additional service providers to better accommodate our customers. muvee will not share personal information with any other third parties without your permission, unless required by law enforcement action, subpoena, or local law.

muvee or its related entities could merge with or be acquired by another business entity or some or all of their respective assets could be acquired. If such a combination or acquisition occurs, muvee will make every reasonable effort to notify you in the event we share with the merging or acquiring entity some or all of your personal information to continue serving you.

  6. ### Your choices

muvee gives you the choice of receiving a variety of information that complements our products and services. You can subscribe to receive certain product- and service-specific information and muvee-wide marketing communications. muvee-wide communications may include new product information, special offers, or an invitation to participate in market research.

  7. ### Your privacy preferences and opting out

#### Non-subscription services

muvee will not use your personal information for a different purpose than the one stated when you provided your data. Examples of unrelated uses include sending communications about special offers, product information, and marketing messages

#### Subscription services

To opt-out of receiving communications you have expressly requested (such as e-mail newsletters, software updates, etc.), use (any of) the following method(s):

    * Select the e-mail _“opt-out”_ or _“unsubscribe”_ link, or follow the opt-out instructions included in each subscription communication
    * Write to: [unsubscribe@muvee.com](mailto:unsubscribe@muvee.com) – be sure to provide your name, e-mail and relevant information about your muvee subscriptions and registrations.
  8. ### Your information and third-party companies

Certain muvee services are linked with those from unrelated third-party companies, some of which offer you the option to share with both muvee and the third party personal data you provide. Examples include the ability to register software products from multiple vendors from a single muvee Web page, to request communications from muvee marketing or solution partners, or to enable order completion through a reseller. We will not share your personal information with those third-party companies unless you make that choice.

  9. ### Access to and accuracy of your information

muvee strives to keep your personal information accurate. We have implemented technology, management processes and policies to maintain customer data accuracy. We will provide you with access to your information, including making reasonable effort to provide you with online access and the opportunity to change your information.

  10. ### Keeping your information secure

muvee is committed to protecting the information you provide us. To prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, to maintain data accuracy, and to ensure the appropriate use of the information, muvee has in place appropriate physical and managerial procedures to safeguard the information we collect.

muvee and its online transaction partner use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption when collecting or transferring sensitive data such as credit card information. SSL encryption is designed to make the information unreadable by anyone but us. This security measure is working when you see either the symbol of an unbroken key or closed lock (depending on your browser) on the bottom of your browser window.

Credit card numbers are used only for processing payment and are not used for other purposes. As part of real-time payment processing, our online transaction partner uses fraud management techniques. This service gives you and muvee an extra level of security to guard against credit card fraud to protect your financial data.

  11. ### Changes to this Statement

If there are updates to the terms of the muvee Online Privacy Statement, we will post those changes and update the revision date in this document, so you will always know what information we collect online, how we use it, and what choices you have. For material changes to this Statement, muvee will provide notification to affected customers.

  12. ### Contacting us

We value your opinions. If you have comments or questions about our privacy policy, please send them to: [contact@muvee.com](mailto:contact@muvee.com)

## How muvee Uses Cookies on muvee.com and in Third-Party Ads Cookies

A _“cookie”_ is a small data file transferred by a website to your computer’s hard drive. muvee sends cookies when you surf our site, make purchases, request or personalize information, or register yourself for certain services. Accepting the cookies used on our site does not give us access to your personal information, but we may use the cookies to identify your computer. Cookies are typically classified as either _“session”_ cookies or _“permanent”_ cookies.

  * _“Session”_ cookies do not stay on your computer after you leave our website or close your browser. The aggregate information collected permits us to analyze traffic patterns on our site. This can enable us over time to provide a better experience on our site by improving content or personalization and making our site easier to use.
  * _“Permanent”_ cookies are those that remain on your computer. They are used to facilitate shopping, personalization and registration services. For example, cookies can keep track of what you have selected to purchase as you continue to shop and allow you to enter your password only once on Web pages where a login is required. “Permanent” cookies can be manually removed by the user. Most browsers automatically accept cookies by default, but you can usually refuse cookies or selectively accept certain cookies by adjusting the preferences in your browser. If you turn off cookies, there may be some features of our site that will not be available to you and some Web pages may not display properly. You can find information on popular browsers and how to adjust your cookie preferences at the following websites: 

Microsoft Internet Explorer: <http://www.microsoft.com/info/cookies.htm>  
Netscape Navigator: <http://www.netscape.com/legal_notices/cookies.htm>

## Third-party media companies

muvee may use third-party media companies to place ads for muvee products or services on other companies’ websites. muvee may also place third-party ads on the muvee.com or related websites. If you view a Web page where muvee ads appear, the online media company may place a cookie on your computer. This allows the online media company to recognize the computer when it is used to return to that site, or to measure advertising response. This data is anonymous and is not linked to personal data on the user’s computer or any muvee databases.

## External Email Disclaimer

Any email sent by muvee is intended only for the named person or entity to which it is addressed and contains valuable business information that is proprietary, privileged, confidential and/or otherwise protected from disclosure. If you receive an email from muvee in error, any review, use dissemination, distribution or copying of this email is strictly prohibited. Please notify the sender immediately of the error and please delete the email from your system, retaining no copies in any media. We appreciate your cooperation.
